Jackson, Mississippi. I, Amanda Seals, your favorite artistic intellectual, will be in your city for the first time ever, by the way.
This Wednesday, as a part of the Voices for a Just World lecture series put together by Mississippi for a Just World and Tougaloo College.
I love saying that, Tougaloo, Tougaloo, Tougaloo, Tougaloo, Tougaloo.
So I'm going to be at Tougaloo College, and don't play with me.
The doors are at 530.
We start at 6 p.m.
Now, those of you all who can't make it in person, it's all good.
Yes, you will be able to watch the full live stream event with Black With No Chaser.
But if you can make it, I hope to see you at Tougaloo College, Tougaloo, Tougaloo, Tougaloo, Tougaloo, Tougaloo, Tougaloo, Tougaloo.
This Wednesday, February 11th.
Buy my latest book, What Would the Ancestors Say? and get it signed.
Join me so we can talk about where we are and where we need to be going.
This is my first time I miss making the best time.